flashtat.com 2017-06-18

# Metallic Temporary Tattoo | Privacy Policy | Flash Tattoos

This Application collects some Personal Data from its Users.

## Data Controller and Owner

Flash Tattoos - Austin, Texas

**Owner contact email:** support@flashtat.com

## Types of Data collected

Among the types of Personal Data that this Application collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookies, Usage data, company name, first name, last name, phone number, email address, state, ZIP/Postal code, date of birth and city.

Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.  
The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Application.  
Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by this Application or by the owners of third party services used by this Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.  
Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services.

Users are responsible for any Personal Data of third parties obtained, published or shared through this Application and confirm that they have the third party's consent to provide the Data to the Owner.

## Mode and place of processing the Data

### Methods of processing

The Data Controller processes the Data of Users in a proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Data Controller, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time.

### Place

The Data is processed at the Data Controller's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact the Data Controller.

### Retention time

The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request that the Data Controller suspend or remove the data.

## The use of the collected Data

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics, Contacting the User, Content commenting, Displaying content from external platforms, Handling payments, Interaction with external social networks and platforms, Managing contacts and sending messages, Managing support and contact requests and Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting.

The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document.

## Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

### Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

#### Google Analytics (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

#### Analytics collected directly (This Application)

This Application uses an internal analytics system that does not involve third parties.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

#### Google AdWords conversion tracking (Google Inc.)

Google AdWords conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google Inc. that connects data from the Google AdWords advertising network with actions performed on this Application.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

### Contacting the User

#### Contact form (This Application)

By filling in the contact form with their Data, the User authorizes this Application to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.

Personal Data collected: company name, email address, first name, last name and phone number.

#### Mailing List or Newsletter (This Application)

By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning this Application. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to this Application or after making a purchase.

Personal Data collected: city, date of birth, email address, first name, last name, state and ZIP/Postal code.

### Content commenting

Content commenting services allow Users to make and publish their comments on the contents of this Application.  
Depending on the settings chosen by the Owner, Users may also leave anonymous comments. If there is an email address among the Personal Data provided by the User, it may be used to send notifications of comments on the same content. Users are responsible for the content of their own comments.  
If a content commenting service provided by third parties is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the comment service is installed, even when Users do not use the content commenting service.

#### Facebook Comments (Facebook, Inc.)

Facebook Comments is a content commenting service provided by Facebook, Inc. enabling the User to leave comments and share them on the Facebook platform.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

#### Disqus (Disqus)

Disqus is a content commenting service provided by Big Heads Labs Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies, Usage data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy) – [Opt out](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/1657951)

### Displaying content from external platforms

This type of services allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Application and interact with them.  
This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

#### Instagram widget (Instagram, Inc.)

Instagram is an image visualization service provided by Instagram, Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/)

#### YouTube video widget (Google Inc.)

YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

#### Vimeo video (Vimeo, LLC)

Vimeo is a video content visualization service provided by Vimeo, LLC that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://vimeo.com/privacy)

#### Google Maps widget (Google)

Google Maps is a maps visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.it/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

#### Google Fonts (Google Inc.)

Google Fonts is a typeface visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.

Personal Data collected: Usage data and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.it/intl/policies/privacy/)

### Handling payments

Payment processing services enable this Application to process payments by credit card, bank transfer or other means. To ensure greater security, this Application shares only the information necessary to execute the transaction with the financial intermediaries handling the transaction.  
Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails containing invoices or notifications concerning the payment.

#### Authorize.Net (Authorize.Net)

Authorize.Net is a payment service provided by Authorize.Net.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/)

#### PayPal (PayPal Inc.)

PayPal is a payment service provided by PayPal Inc., which allows Users to make online payments using their PayPal credentials.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

This type of services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Application.  
The interaction and information obtained through this Application are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.  
This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

#### AddThis (Addthis Inc.)

AddThis is a service provided by Clearspring Technologies Inc., which displays a widget that allows interaction with social networks and external platforms as well as sharing the contents of this Application.  
Depending on the configuration, this service can display widgets belonging to third parties such as the managers of social networks where interactions are shared. In this case, also the third parties that provide the widget will be informed of interactions and Usage Data on the pages where this service is installed.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy)

#### Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets (Pinterest)

The Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Pinterest platform provided by Pinterest Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy)

#### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter)

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy)

#### Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)

The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

### Managing contacts and sending messages

This type of services makes it possible to manage a database of email contacts, phone contacts or any other contact information to communicate with the User.  
These services may also collect data concerning the date and time when the message was viewed by the User, as well as when the User interacted with it, such as by clicking on links included in the message.

#### MailChimp (The Rocket Science Group, LLC.)

MailChimp is an email address management and message sending service provided by The Rocket Science Group, LLC.

Personal Data collected: email address.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)

### Managing support and contact requests

This type of services allows this Application to manage support and contact requests received via email or by other means, such as the contact form.  
The Personal Data processed depend on the information provided by the User in the messages and the means used for communication (e.g. email address).

#### Zendesk (Zendesk)

Zendesk is a support and contact request management service provided by Zendesk Inc.

Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.zendesk.com/company/privacy)

### Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting

This type of services allows this Application and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of this Application by the User.  
This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using Cookies, information that is transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity.

#### AdRoll (Semantic Sugar, Inc.)

AdRoll is an advertising service provided by Semantic Sugar, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy) – [Opt Out](https://info.evidon.com/pub_info/573?v=1&nt=1&nw=false)

## Further information about Personal Data

### Candid

TERMS & CONDITIONS

In addition to the social media platform’s own policies, guidelines and rules, the following are Flash Tattoos™, LLC’s (“Flash Tattoos”) terms and conditions for submitting content on any of our social media pages. 

Use of Flash Tattoos™ Social Media Pages   
Users may post photos, comments, reviews, videos and any other content. Users may also submit feedback, ideas, comments, suggestions, questions, or other information, as appropriate for the purposes of Flash Tattoos™ social media page. Flash Tattoos™ reserves the right, but not the obligation, to remove or edit such content without prior notice for any reason Flash Tattoos™ deems necessary.

By posting or submitting content, you warrant and represent that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to your submission including, but not limited to, all the rights necessary for you to provide, post, upload, input or submit the content. To the extent that the content submitted contains images, photographs, or artistic designs ("Images"), you warrant and represent that (a) you are the copyright owner of any submitted images, or you are a licensee with permission granted by the copyright owner to use the Images in the manner submitted; (b) you have the rights necessary to grant the licenses and sub-licenses described in these Terms of Use (to Flash Tattoos — see “Licensing” below); (c) that any person(s) depicted in any Images, if any, has provided consent to the use of the Images and their likeness.

Nothing in these Terms and Conditions shall be deemed to create an agency, partnership, joint venture, employee-employer or franchise-franchisee relationship, or a business relationship of any kind between Flash Tattoos™ and you or any other person or entity.  
Without limiting the description above, by using this social media page you agree not to:

1\. Abuse, harass, defame, threaten, impersonate or intimidate other users;

2\. Post or transmit, or cause to be posted or transmitted, any content that is infringing, libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, abusive, offensive, profane, or otherwise violates any law or right of any third party;

3\. Use this social media page for any illegal or unauthorized purpose, including violating any local, state, national or international laws including but not limited to infringing any copyright, trademark, trade secret, patent or other proprietary rights of any party;

4\. Post or transmit, or cause to be posted or transmitted, any communication or solicitation designed or intended to obtain private information or personal information of any user including but not limited to any user(s) password, account, or other account details;

5\. Make available by any means (post, submit, comment) any unwanted or unsolicited e-mail, or any other message or comments, to any users including advertising, promotional materials, spam, junk mail, chain letters (or e-mail(s)), pyramid schemes, or any other form of solicitation about any other product or service;

6\. You may not use any photo editing techniques to obscure, remove, or alter in any way any trademark, logo, slogan, or other proprietary information belonging to Flash Tattoos without prior and express written consent. Frame or utilize any “photo-cropping” or framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo, or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) of Flash Tattoos™ without express written consent. 

7\. You may not use any meta tags, descriptions, or any other "hidden text" utilizing Flash Tattoos's name, trademarks, or any copyrighted text;

8\. Submit stories or comments linking to multi-level marketing schemes, pyramid schemes or off-topic content;

9\. Use any robots, spiders, scrapers or any other automated means to access this social media page for any purpose. Additionally, you agree that you will not: (i) take any action that imposes or may impose, in our sole discretion, an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on our website infrastructure; (ii) upload viruses, malware, or any other malicious code; or (iii) bypass or override any measures Flash Tattoos may put in place in order to restrict access to this social media page;

10\. Advertise to, or solicit, any user to buy or sell any products or services. It is also a violation of these rules to use any information obtained from this social media page in order to contact, advertise to, solicit, or sell to any user without their prior explicit consent.

Comments, Feedback and Other Submissions to Flash Tattoos™ 

We welcome your comments and feedback regarding our social media pages, our products and our services. Flash Tattoos™, however, does not accept confidential or proprietary information from any comments or submissions. Accordingly, all comments, feedback, ideas, suggestions, materials, information and other submissions disclosed, submitted or offered to Flash Tattoos™ using this social media page or otherwise (collectively, 'Feedback') are not confidential and will become and remain Flash Tattoos' property. The disclosure, submission or offer of any Feedback will constitute an assignment to Flash Tattoos™ of all worldwide rights, licenses, titles and interests and goodwill in the Comments without payment of any compensation or consideration. Comments submitted by you must not violate any right of any third party, and must not contain any libelous, abusive, obscene or otherwise unlawful material.

Content Management, Review, or Removal

Flash Tattoos is not in any manner responsible for the content of these submissions, communications or materials. Flash Tattoos does not and cannot review and/or screen all materials submitted to or created by users accessing this social media page. You acknowledge that Flash Tattoos, by providing you with the ability to view and distribute user-generated content on this social media page, is merely acting as a passive entity for the dissemination of such content and Flash Tattoos does not undertake, and disclaims, any liabilities or obligations relating to any contents or activities on this social media page. However, Flash Tattoos does reserve the right to block or remove any materials that it determines, in its sole discretion, to be (a) abusive, defamatory, or obscene, (b) fraudulent, deceptive, or misleading, (c) in violation of a copyright, trademark or any other intellectual property right of another, or (d) violates any law (local, state, federal, or international law), regulation or Terms of this social media page, or (e) offensive or otherwise unacceptable to Flash Tattoos. Flash Tattoos reserves the right, but undertakes no obligation or duty, to review, alter, edit, move or remove any submitted materials provided for display or placed on this social media page in any manner, in its sole discretion, without notice. If at any time Flash Tattoos, in its sole discretion, chooses to monitor or moderate submissions on this social media page, Flash Tattoos nonetheless assumes no responsibility or liability for the content and no obligation to modify or remove any inappropriate content; Flash Tattoos is not responsible for the conduct of the user submitting any such content.

User Generated Content   
This social media page contains content of users and other Flash Tattoos licensors. Except as provided within these Terms, you may not copy, modify, translate, publish, broadcast, transmit, distribute, perform, display, or use in commerce any content appearing on or through this social media page.

Flash Tattoos does not endorse, support, sanction, encourage, verify, sponsor, or agree with any comments, opinions, or statements posted in this social media page and expressly disclaims any and all liability in connection with user submissions.

You agree that Flash Tattoos™ and its affiliates are not responsible, and shall have no liability to you, with respect to any information, communication or materials posted by others, including defamatory, offensive or illicit material, including material that violates these Terms. Any material downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of this social media page is done at your own risk and you will be solely responsible for any damage to your computer system or any other electronic device and/or any loss of data that may result from the download of any such material.

Flash Tattoos uses a variety of third-party social media websites and media channels such as Instagram, Facebook, and Twitter ("Social Media Pages") to communicate and interact with our customers. By posting or submitting content to these Social Media Pages, you represent and warrant that you have the lawful right to transmit, distribute and reproduce such content. If submitted content contains images, you represent and warrant that: (a) you are the copyright owner or have obtained the copyright owner's permission to use such images; (b) you hold the rights necessary to grant the licenses and sub-licenses described in these Terms and Conditions (see “Licensing” below); (c) you have obtained the consent of any person(s) depicted in such images. 

Licensing

By posting, displaying, uploading, inputting, providing, transmitting, submitting, content to Flash Tattoos’ website or Social Media Pages or if you are contacted by Flash Tattoos and consent, by any means, to the use of any content on our website or any Social Media Pages, you grant Flash Tattoos a perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, royalty-free, sub-licensable license, to copy, distribute, reproduce, use, modify, adapt, publish, translate, transmit, disclose, publicly perform, and publicly display the user content (in whole or in part) and to incorporate such user content into other works in any format or medium now known or later developed for any and all commercial or non-commercial purposes.

Indemnification 

You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless Flash Tattoos, and its affiliates, and their respective officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors and suppliers (collectively the "Indemnified Parties") from and against all losses, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys' fees, resulting from any violation of these Terms and conditions or any activity related to your account (including negligent or wrongful conduct), by you or any other person accessing this social media page by using your account.

Contact Us

If any problems may arise with this social media page or any content, you agree that your sole remedy is to cease using this social media page. Please report any violations of the Terms and Conditions on our social media pages to kirsten@flashtat.com. If there are issues with content infringing upon copyrights, trademarks, or any other intellectual property please contact our Intellectual Property Associate at kurt@flashtat.com.

## Information about Cookies

### Analytics

These Cookies are necessary for the functioning of the services filed under the section ”Analytics”.

#### _ut*, _ga*

Google Analytics Cookies.

### Displaying content from external platforms

These Cookies are necessary for the functioning of the services filed under the section ”Displaying content from external platforms”.

#### ACTIVITY, APISID, GED_PLAYLIST_ACTIVITY, GEUP, HSID, LOGIN_INFO, PREF, SAPISID, SID, SSID, VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE, YSC, __utma, __utmc, __utmz, s_gl, wide

YouTube video widget Cookies.

### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

These Cookies are necessary for the functioning of the services filed under the section ”Interaction with external social networks and platforms”.

#### __atuvc

AddThis Cookies.

Since the installation of third party Cookies and other tracking systems through the services used within this Application cannot be technically controlled by the Owner, any specific references to Cookies and tracking systems installed by third parties are to be considered indicative. In order to obtain complete information, consult the privacy policy for the respective third party services listed in this document.

## Additional information about Data collection and processing

### Legal action

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related services.  
The User declares to be aware that the Data Controller may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

### Additional information about User's Personal Data

In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

### System logs and maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.

### The rights of Users

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above.

This Application does not support “Do Not Track” requests.  
To determine whether any of the third party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request that the Data Controller remove the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users.

### Information about this privacy policy

The Data Controller is responsible for this privacy policy, prepared starting from the modules provided by Iubenda and hosted on Iubenda's servers.

### Definitions and legal references

#### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.

#### Usage Data

Information collected automatically from this Application (or third party services employed in this Application), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Application, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.

#### User

The individual using this Application, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refers.

#### Data Subject

The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.

#### Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the Data Controller to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy.

#### Data Controller (or Owner)

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Application. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Application.

#### This Application

The hardware or software tool by which the Personal Data of the User is collected.

#### Cookies

Small piece of data stored in the User's device.

#### Legal information

Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies.

This privacy policy relates solely to this Application.

Latest update: April 20, 2015
